Preliminary Inventory of the Arnold Beichman papers,
Hoover Institution Archives
- Correspondence, 1935-2006 (Box 110-113)
  - Kaiser, Philip, 1937-1991 (Box-folder 110: 61)
  - Kaiser, Robert G., 1975 (Box-folder 110: 62)
  - Kanza, R. Thomas, 1982 (Box-folder 111: 1)
  - Kempton, Murray, 1950 (Box-folder 111: 2)
  - Kendall, Bridget, 1993 (Box-folder 111: 3)
  - Kessler, Martin (Basic Books), 1989 (Box-folder 111: 4)
  - Kirkpatrick, Jeane, 1981-1986 (Box-folder 111: 5)
  - Klinghoffer, David, 1993 (Box-folder 111: 6)
  - Kramer, Hilton, 1988 (Box-folder 111: 7)
  - Kristol, Bea (Gertrude Himmelfarb), 1979-1986 (Box-folder 111: 8)
  - Kristol, Elizabeth, 1979 (Box-folder 111: 9)
  - Kristol, Irving, 1953-1994 (Box-folder 111: 10)
  - Kristol, William, 1998 (Box-folder 111: 11)
  - Kuehnelt-Leddin, Erik von, 1982 (Box-folder 111: 12)
  - La Follette, Karen, 1990 (Box-folder 111: 13)
  - Landes, David, 1976 (Box-folder 111: 14)
  - Lasky, Melvin, 1979-1989 (Box-folder 111: 15)
  - Lavine, Hal, undated (Box-folder 111: 16)
  - Lehmann-Haupt, Christopher, 1996 (Box-folder 111: 17)
  - Lelyveld, Arthur, 1935-1991 (Box-folder 111: 18)
  - Lelyveld, Joseph, 1978-1991 (Box-folder 111: 19)
  - Lenczowski, George, 1990 (Box-folder 111: 20)
  - Lenzner, Robert, undated (Box-folder 111: 21)
  - Lerner, Max, 1985-1991 (Box-folder 111: 22)
  - Levitas, Mitchel, 1976 (Box-folder 111: 23)
  - Lewis, Flora, 1984 (Box-folder 111: 24)
  - Lipset, Seymour Martin, 1983-1991 (Box-folder 111: 25)
  - Manning, Margaret ( ), 1981 (Box-folder 111: 26)
  - Mansfield, Harvey, 1989 (Box-folder 111: 27)
  - Marcus, Steven, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 111: 28)
  - Marples, David, 1989-1991 (Box-folder 111: 29)
  - Matlock, John, 1990 (Box-folder 111: 30)
  - McCarthy, Mary, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 111: 31)
  - McDougall, Walter, 1997 (Box-folder 111: 32)
  - Meany, George, 1949-1975 (Box-folder 111: 33)
  - Mehring, Walter, undated (Box-folder 111: 34)
  - Meyer, Herbert, 1982-1991 (Box-folder 111: 35)
  - Miler, N. Scott, 1981 (Box-folder 111: 36)
  - Minogue, Kenneth, 1974-1992 (Box-folder 111: 37)
  - Morgan, Ted, 1999 (Box-folder 111: 38)
  - Morton, Robert, 1989 (Box-folder 111: 39)
  - Moynihan, Patrick and Elizabeth, undated (Box-folder 111: 40)
  - Nabokov, Nicolas, 1949 (Box-folder 111: 41)
  - Nash, George, 1983 (Box-folder 111: 42)
  - Newman, Peter ( ), 1982 (Box-folder 111: 43)
  - Newton, Hugh, 1999 (Box-folder 111: 44)
  - Nisbet, Robert, 1965-1975 (Box-folder 111: 45)
  - Nixon, Richard, 1958 (Box-folder 111: 46)
  - Palm, Charles (Hoover Institution), 1991 (Box-folder 111: 47)
  - Pines, Burton, 1985 (Box-folder 111: 48)
  - Pipes, Richard, 1980-1997 (Box-folder 111: 49)
  - Podhoretz, John, 1980-1994 (Box-folder 111: 50)
  - Podhoretz, Norman, 1971-1994 (Box-folder 111: 51)
  - Powell, Anthony, 1969-1979 (Box-folder 111: 52)
  - Prager, Dennis, 1985 (Box-folder 111: 53)
  - Pruden, Wesley, 1991 (Box-folder 111: 54)
  - Radio Free Europe/Radio Liberty, 1989 (Box-folder 112: 1)
  - Raditsa, Bogdan, 1971 (Box-folder 112: 2)
  - Raisian, John (Hoover Institution), 1993 (Box-folder 112: 3)
  - Ranum, Orest, 1969 (Box-folder 112: 4)
  - Raphael, Adam, undated (Box-folder 112: 5)
  - Raphael, Chaim, 1966-1994 (Box-folder 112: 6)
  - , 1988 (Box-folder 112: 7)
  - Reed, John, 1991 (Box-folder 112: 8)
  - Rees, David, 1966-1968 (Box-folder 112: 9)
  - Revel, Jean-François, 1977 (Box-folder 112: 10)
  - Richard, Ivor, 1975 (Box-folder 112: 11)
  - Richler, Mordechai, 1986-1998 (Box-folder 112: 12)
  - Riesman, David, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 112: 13)
  - Robert S. and Grace B. Kerr Foundation, 1988 (Box-folder 112: 14)
  - Roche, John, 1983-1990 (Box-folder 112: 15)
  - Rosenthal, A.M., 1969-1990 (Box-folder 112: 16)
  - Rossant, Murray, 1979 (Box-folder 112: 17)
  - Rostow, Eugene, 1982 (Box-folder 112: 18)
  - Ruddy, Frank, 2006 (Box-folder 112: 19)
  - Rusher, Bill, 1994 (Box-folder 112: 20)
  - Safire, William, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 112: 21)
  - Salisbury, Harrison, 1970 (Box-folder 112: 22)
  - Schapiro, Leonard, 1960 (Box-folder 112: 23)
  - Schlesinger, Arthur, Jr., 1976-1987 (Box-folder 112: 24)
  - Scully, Michael, 1992 (Box-folder 112: 25)
  - Segal, Martin, 1973 (Box-folder 112: 26)
  - Seligman, Daniel, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 112: 27)
  - Shanker, Albert, 1991 (Box-folder 112: 28)
  - Sheed, Wilfrid, 1974 (Box-folder 112: 29)
  - Siegelman, Philip, 1990 (Box-folder 112: 30)
  - Silber, John, 1974 (Box-folder 112: 31)
  - Skidelsky, Robert, 1992 (Box-folder 112: 32)
  - Sobran, Joe, 1986 (Box-folder 112: 33)
  - Sofaer, Marian, 1990 (Box-folder 112: 34)
  - Sowell, Thomas, 1984-1993 (Box-folder 112: 35)
  - Speed, Keith, 1976 (Box-folder 112: 36)
  - Stanton, George, 1982 (Box-folder 112: 37)
  - Starr, Roger, 1994 (Box-folder 112: 38)
  - Stockdale, James B., 1983-1984 (Box-folder 112: 39)
  - Sullivan, Frank, 1950 (Box-folder 112: 40)
  - Suzman, Helen, 1965-1994 (Box-folder 112: 41)
  - Symons, Julian, 1975-1986 (Box-folder 112: 42)
  - Szamuely, Tibor, 1966-1970 (Box-folder 112: 43)
  - Thompson, Eva, 1983-1994 (Box-folder 112: 44)
  - Tiro, Hasan di, 1982-1994 (Box-folder 112: 45)
  - Trilling, Diana, 1953-1959, 1961-1996 (Box-folder 112: 46-47)
  - Trilling, Lionel, 1971 (Box-folder 113: 1)
  - Truman, David, 1966-1972 (Box-folder 113: 2)
  - Tyrmand, Leopold, 1978-1982 (Box-folder 113: 3)
  - Tyrrell, W. Emmett, 1978-1984 (Box-folder 113: 4)
  - Ulam, Adam, 1988 (Box-folder 113: 5)
  - Vaizey, John, 1972 (Box-folder 113: 6)
  - Van Houten, Jan, 1982-1984 (Box-folder 113: 7)
  - Viereck, Peter, undated (Box-folder 113: 8)
  - Walker, Richard L., 1998-2001 (Box-folder 113: 9)
  - , 1984-1994 (Box-folder 113: 10)
  - Wattenberg, Ben, 1985 (Box-folder 113: 11)
  - Wechsler, Nancy, 1984 (Box-folder 113: 12)
  - Whalen, Richard, 1989 (Box-folder 113: 13)
  - Wick, Charles Z. (United States Information Agency), 1986-1987 (Box-folder 113: 14)
  - Wiesel, Elie, 1978 (Box-folder 113: 15)
  - Wieseltier, Leon, 1983 (Box-folder 113: 16)
  - Wildavsky, Aaron, 1973 (Box-folder 113: 17)
  - Will, George, 1991 (Box-folder 113: 18)
  - Willcox, Christopher ( ), 1988 (Box-folder 113: 19)
  - Wohlstetter, Albert, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 113: 20)
  - Wolfe, Tom, 1965-1992 (Box-folder 113: 21)
  - Wood, Robert (University of Massachusetts), 1973 (Box-folder 113: 22)
  - Worthington, Peter, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 113: 23)
  - Wouk, Herman, 1971-2005 (Box-folder 113: 24)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1952-1985 (Box-folder 113: 25-26)
- Articles, essays, and school compositions by Arnold Beichman, 1934-1984 (Box-folder 113: 27)